Salem Witchcraft Papers from the Essex County Court Archives
University of Virginia Library
- Volume 2
  - Order of Benjamin Nurse et al. for Payment, Case of Rebecca Nurse, ecca2146
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 146.
  - Order of Joseph & Abigail Procter for Payment, Cases of John & Elizabeth Procter, ecca2147
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 147.
  - Order of John Nurse et al. for Payment, Case of Rebecca Nurse, ecca2148
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 148.
  - Order of Abigail Hobbs for Payment, ecca2149
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 149.
  - Petition of John & Annis King for Restitution for Dorcas Hoar, ecca2151
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 151.
  - Order of George & Hannah Abbott for Payment, Case of Mary Esty, ecca2152
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 152.
  - Petition of Benjamin Procter for Restitution, ecca2153
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 153.
  - Order of Joseph Esty for Payment, Case of Mary Esty, ecca2154
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 154.
  - Order of Thomas Carrier for Payment, ecca2155
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 155.
  - Order of Mary & Abigail How for Payment, Case of Elizabeth How, ecca2156
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 156.
  - Order of George Burroughs Jr. for Payment, Case of George Burroughs, ecca2157
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 157.
  - Division of Money in Burroughs Restitution, ecca2158
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 158.
  - Order of Peter Thomas et al. for Payment, Case of George Burroughs, ecca2159
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 159.
  - Petition of the Children of George Burroughs, ecca2160
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 160.
  - Letter of Mary Burroughs, Case of George Burroughs, ecca2161
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 161.
  - Petition of the Children of George Burroughs for Restitution, ecca2162
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 162.
  - Letter of Rebecca Fowle, Case of George Burroughs, ecca2163
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 163.
  - Order of Jeremiah Burroughs for Payment, Case of George Burroughs, ecca2164
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 164.
  - Order of William Wardwell et al. for Payment, Cases of Samuel & Sarah Wardwell, ecca2165
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 165.
  - Order of Rebecca Eames for Payment, ecca2166
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 166.
  - Petition of Samuel Wardwell Jr. for Restitution for Sarah Wardwell, ecca2167
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 167.
  - Petition of Nathaniel Dane et al. for Restitution, ecca2168
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 168.
  - Petition of Elizabeth Johnson Jr. for Restitution, ecca2169
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 169.
  - Petition of Peter Osgood for Restitution for Mary Osgood, ecca2170
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 170.
  - Order of John & Mary Stanyan for Payment, Case of Mary Bradbury, ecca2171
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 171.
  - Order of John Parker for Payment, Case of Mary Parker, ecca2172
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 172.
  - Order of Mary Post for Payment, ecca2173
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 173.
  - Order of Mary Procter for Payment, Cases of John & Elizabeth Procter, ecca2174
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 174.
  - Petition of Sarah Parker for Restitution, ecca2175
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 175.
  - Order of Rachel Slue for Payment, ecca2176
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 176.
  - Petition of Mary DeRich for Restitution, ecca2177
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 177.
  - Order of the Superior Court of Judicature Regarding Payment of Court Costs, ecca2178
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 178.
  - Superior Court of Judicature: Statement of Sums Due, ecca2179
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 179.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by Robert Lord, Blacksmith, ecca2180
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 180.
  - Letter of Nehemiah Jewett to Stephen Sewell, ecca2181
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 181.
  - Order of Lawrence Lacey for Payment, Case of Mary Lacey Sr., ecca2182
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 182.
  - Petition of Philip English for Restitution, ecca2184
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 184.
  - Recognizance for Dorothy Good by Samuel Ray, ecca2185
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 185.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by Thomas Fosse, Jailkeeper, ecca2186
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 186.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by Samuel Graves, Constable, ecca2187
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 187.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by William Baker, Constable, ecca2188
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 188.